

CONTACT

- 🔁 rageshkarunakaran@gmail.com
- **(**, 7200932145 / 7010569175
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/ ragesh-karunakaran-0aa055241
- Chennai

Nationality:

Indian

Date of Birth:

18-05-1995

SKILLS

HTML 5
CSS 3
Bootstrap 5
Javascript
Jquery
scss,sass,less
Adobe Photoshop
Adobe XD
Adobe illustrator
materialize css

LANGUAGES

Tamil English Malayalam

RAGESH KARUNAKARAN

Front-end UI Developer

PROFILE

4 years experienced Web Designer with proven success in building successful webpage & predictive models. To have a growth oriented and challenging career, where I can contribute my knowledge and skills to the organization and enhance my experience through continuous learning and teamwork.

EDUCATION

BE (CSE) | Cape Institute of Technology, Kanyakumari

Jun 2015 - Apr 2018

DCSE | Cape Polytechnic College , Nagercoil

Jun 2012 - Apr 2014

EXPERIENCE

Front-end Developer | Guardianlink (Appstar applications Pvt Ltd), CHENNAI Nov 2020 - Present

- Working on NFT Marketplace and Landing websites.
- Working on Crypto Development Websites. Closely worked with Business Analyst to understand the business requirements.
- Worked more than 20+ client projects including in major segments of Blockchain NFTs and ICO.
- Supported for in house design and development including emailers along with mobile marvel and web marvels.

Web Designer | Cube45 eCommerce Pvt Ltd, CHENNAI

Jun 2018 - Nov 2020

- Created more than 20 websites using Theme Customization Perform activities to optimize websites for search engine optimization.
- Design and development of "Malaf" medical project using HTML, Bootstrap4, CSS 3 and Javascript. PSD Layout to HTML Conversion. Perform activities to optimize websites for search engine optimization

Graphic Designer | TNQ Technologies, CHENNAI

May 2014 - Feb 2015

- Working on Adobe Photoshop
- Working on Adobe illustrator

EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Volleyball Player | Cape Institute of Technology, Kanyakumari

Nov 2015 - Oct 2018

Kabadi Player | Cape Polytechnic College, Kanyakumari

Jun 2012 - Jun 2014

COURSES

React JS

Aug 2022 - Present

PORTFOLIO

https://www.jump.trade/

https://www.guardianlink.io/blog

https://adgrohairclinicannanagar.com/

https://edu-med.herokuapp.com/

https://preludesys.herokuapp.com/

https://www.jumptrade.in/

https://www.guardianlink.io/

https://nft1.bafdemo.com/

https://nft.latimes.com/

https://www.turnkeytown.com/

https://www.inoru.com/

https://www.blockchainappfactory.com/

https://www.chaincella.com/

https://gigada.inorudemo.com/

https://foodgenix.inorudemo.com/

https://lekture.inorudemo.com/

https://dateduo.inorudemo.com/

https://polycruz.io/

https://www.cube45.org/

https://www.jump.trade/blog